What are you talking about?
Why should we have to share
these healing crystals with you?
Your pet lizard has
healing powers, you know.
But you never fight on the front
line, so who are you to talk?
You don't need to use any crystals.
Of course I do.
You're the popular one
around here, Silica.
I can't expect the boys
to help me when I need it.
Oh, come on.
It's not like that.
Fine. I don't care.
You want my items?
Take them.
But I'm never going to
team up with you again.
I know there's a ton of other parties out
there who'd love to have me on their side.
Wait! Don't go!
Silica!
I am afraid of my
back-to-face I am now in the
back-to-face I am now in
the future I am now in the sky
Here is a beautiful heart I
am here I am in the dream I
can't believe that I'm not my
body When it comes to my body,
I take my breath As long as I'm feeling,
I will be broken I can't believe that
I'm not my heart When I see myself,
I'm feeling weak I'm feeling weak,
you can't believe that I'm
not my heart I'm feeling weak,
when I see you in a
clear universe A .M .S.
I wanna always do it too.
I'll give you everything I have!
I'm out of healing crystals!
Inna!
Inna! Inna!
Ah!
Inna…
Pina!
Don't leave me all alone here!
What's that feather?
It's Pina.
My best friend.
You're one of those
beast tamers, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
If I got here sooner, I
could have saved your friend.
No.
It's all my fault.
I was stupid to think I could make
it through the forest on my own.
Thank you for saving me.
You did what you could. That feather.
Check and see if it has an
item name attached to it.
Hey, don't cry.
That means Pina's heart's still here.
There's a chance you can revive it.
No way, really? Mm-hmm.
On the south side of floor 47, There's a
field dungeon called the Hill of Memories.
I heard somewhere that the flower
growing at the top can revive familiars.
4.47, huh?
I'd offer to go get it for you.
All you'd have to do is pay for the trip.
The thing is, the flower won't bloom
unless the familiars' master's there.
Thank you so much for telling me about it.
If I work hard to raise my
level, then someday I could...
Sure, but the time limit's
three days to revive it.
No way.
It's all my fault.
I'm so sorry, Pina.
It's okay.
You have three days.
Take this equipment.
It should boost you five or six levels.
And if I tag along, I'm sure
everything will work out.
But why would you do all this for me?
I'll tell you, but only if you
promise not to laugh, okay?
I promise I won't.
All right.
It's because you look
like my little sister.
I'm sorry.
Mom, I know this isn't enough
cold to pay you back, but...
No, it's cool.
Besides, it works with why I'm here.
We'll be helping each other out.
Okay, then.
My name's Silica.
My name's Kirito.
I guess we'll be working
together for a little while.
Hey, look! It's Silica!
It took you a long time to get back.
We were getting worried.
You want to team up with us?
We'll take you wherever you want to go.
That's really nice of you to offer, but...
Well, I've sort of already agreed
to be in a party with him, so...
Okay, later, bye!
I didn't mean to put you
on the spot like that.
Didn't know you had fans.
You must be popular.
No.
They don't take me seriously.
They want me to be their mascot.
Maybe they're right.
They call me dragon tamer and
I guess it went to my head.
Don't worry about it.
We'll make it in time!
Promise.
Do you live around here, Kirito?
I'm on floor 50.
It's kind of far, so I was
thinking of getting a room tonight.
If you stay, I'll take you
out for some cheesecake.
It's really good here.
Well, if it isn't silica.
Wow, you made it out of the forest alive.
Good for you, girl.
Something wrong?
Oh, no, nothing. Hang on.
What happened to your
little friend the lizard?
Did it run away?
Peanut died saving me.
But I'm gonna get Peanut back. Really?
I guess you'll be heading for
the Hill of Memories then.
I wonder if you'll be able
to clear it at your level.
Of course she will.
It's not that difficult to level.
Oh, God, this girl seduced another player.
No, it's not difficult, but
you don't look that strong.
Come on.
Why does she have to be so mean?
Well, is Sword Art Online your first MMO?
Uh-huh.
A lot of people's personalities
change when they play games online.
And some actually like playing
the game as the bad guy.
You see how our cursors are green?
Well, if you commit a crime against another
player, your cursor's gonna turn orange.
Then they become what's
called a red player.
The worst, also known as player killers.
They're all about murder.
They kill other players?
In a normal game, they roleplay as the
bad guy, have some laughs, and it's cool.
But Sword Art Online isn't normal.
It's definitely not a game.
Kirito?
I'm sorry.
Well, I think you're good, so...
I mean, you saved me after all.
Looks like you cheered me up instead.
Thank you, Silica.
Wow, where the heck is
our cheesecake already?
Excuse me!
Our dessert hasn't shown up yet!
I wonder if he'd laugh if I told
him I wanted to talk some more.
Silica, you still awake?
Kirito!
I forgot to tell you some stuff about
floor 47, but it can wait till tomorrow.
No, now's fine!
Actually, I was just thinking
I should ask you about…
That was so close.
What's up? Something wrong?
No, nothing.
What's that thing do, Kirito?
It's a mirage sphere.
It's pretty.
This is the town area of 447
and that's the Hill of Memories.
I was thinking if we
take this route, we can
What's wrong?
Who's there?
Um, who was it?
An eavesdropper.
But they can't.
I mean, you can't hear through
a door unless you knock first.
But if your listening skill
is high enough, you can.
It takes practice.
Not that many players have it.
Why would they want to listen to us? Huh?
Wow!
This place is like a dream!
I know.
The whole floor is covered in flowers.
That's why they call it the Flower Garden.
Couples!
Silica?
Nothing!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's wrong? Nothing.
Nothing at all. Come on.
Okay.
What's that for?
If anything bad happens while we're in
here, I'm gonna tell you to warp out, okay?
When I do, use this crystal.
You can jump to any town with it.
But... No buts. Use it.
I understand.
Let's get going.
If we take this path, it'll lead
us right to the Hill of Memories.
Um, Kirito...
Calm down!
That thing's not that strong!
Oh, Jimmy, don't save me!
But don't look! Save me!
But don't look!
That'll be...difficult.
Darn you!
Look me down! Now!
Do you see anything?
Not really.
I hope you don't mind me asking,
but what's your sister like?
Why do you want to know?
Well, you said I looked like her.
I know it's not polite to ask about
your real life, but what's she like?
I call her my little sister,
but she's really my cousin.
We were raised like
brother and sister since
we were babies so I doubt she even knows.
But I know and I guess that's
the reason I avoided her.
Our grandfather's really strict.
When I was eight he made us
take classes at the local
kendo dojo but after a
couple years I stopped going.
Grandpa beat the hell out of me for that.
That's awful.
Anyway then my sister stood up
for me and told him to stop.
She said she'd train hard
for both of us and she did.
She trained hard.
She even made it to the
nationals. She did. How awesome?
Yeah I've always felt guilty
for putting her through that.
I wouldn't doubt it if she hates me.
God knows she could have
been doing something else.
Maybe that's why I wanted
to help you in a weird way.
It makes me feel like I'm paying her back.
There it is.
If you don't mind me saying you're wrong.
I don't think she hates you at all.
She wouldn't work that hard
for you if she didn't like you.
Promise and I bet she even loves kendo.
There you go again making me feel.
Maybe you're right.
Man, I hope so.
Okay, then.
I'm gonna do my best, too.
Kiriko!
Is that reviving flower around here?
Yeah, over there.
Go ahead, pick it up.
You sure it'll bring Pina back to life?
Uh-huh.
I'm so glad.
There's a bunch of strong
monsters lurking around here.
Let's revive it when we get back to town.
I'm sure Pina would want it that way.
Okay.
Is something wrong?
Whoever's hiding out there, come out.
Now.
Rosalia?
If you saw through my
hiding skill so easy,
your detection skill must
be really high, Swordsman.
Ooh, it looks like you were successful
getting your hands on the Name Flower.
Congratulations.
Now, hand it over before you get hurt.
What are you talking about?
No one's handing anything over, Rosalia.
Not to you.
Or the Orange Gill.
Or should I say Titan's hand?
You're their leader, right?
Nice.
But Rosalia's cursor is green.
It's an easy trick.
The green members find their victims.
Then, they lure them straight to
the orange players for the ambush.
That was one of your pals last night
eavesdropping on us, wasn't it?
Then, the reason you were in that
party with me and the others was to...
How perceptive.
I was observing their strength and watching
them earn all that beautiful money.
You were who I was excited about and
I was so sad when you left the party.
But then you told me you
were getting a rare item!
What I want to know is if you knew
about us, why did you bring her here?
Are you dumb or does she have
you wrapped around her finger?
Nope, you're wrong both times.
See, I've been looking
all over for you, Rosalia.
What are you talking about?
Remember ten days ago, you attacked
a guild called the Silver Flags?
The leader survived.
Ford didn't.
Oh, the losers with no money.
Their leader went back and forth,
from the warp point to the
front lines morning till night,
and with tears in his eyes, he begged
everyone he met to avenge his dead friends.
But he didn't want you killed.
No, he wanted you to go to prison.
Do you have any idea how he felt?
Can't say I do.
Only idiots take this seriously.
So what if we kill someone here?
There's no proof dying
here means you're dead IRL.
Anyway, it's time you started
worrying about yourselves.
Kirito, there's too many of them.
We should get out of here.
No, it's okay.
You'll be safe if you stay here.
Keep the crystal handy till I say so.
Okay, but...
Kirito!
Kirito?
Dressed in black, one-handed, no shield.
Holy crap, it's the Black Swordsman.
Rosalia, that guy.
He's the beater who plays
solo on the front lines.
He's with the assault team.
No way he is.
Why would someone from the assault
team be all the way down here?
Go on, take him out and take
everything he owns. Die!
I've got to save him. He won't last.
What's going on?
What the hell, you idiots?
Kill him already!
410 seconds, give or take.
That's about the total damage the
seven of you can inflict on me.
I'm level 78.
I got 14,500 HP.
My battle healing skill auto-regenerates
600 points every 10 seconds.
We could stand here all day
and you wouldn't get anywhere.
That's not possible. Wanna bet?
If your numbers are high
enough, you're invincible.
Miss that use leveling
systems are unfair that way.
My client spent his entire fortune on this
warp crystal and he'll
get his money's worth.
It's been set to the
coordinates of the prison.
And I'm sending all of you bastards there.
Well, I'm green, and if you
hurt me, you'll go orange.
I'm a solo player, got it.
I don't care if I have to play
as orange for a couple of days.
I'm really sorry, Silica.
This whole time I was using
you as bait to catch him.
I thought you'd be scared if
I told you the truth about me.
I could never be scared of you.
Because you're a good person.
Um, do you really have to go?
Yeah, I've been away from the
front lines for five days.
I need to get back.
I think it's Koya with the assault team.
I could try for a hundred
years and never make it.
Um, I...
You know, levels are just numbers.
And a person's strength in
this world is just an illusion.
Sure, it's cool and all, but there
are more important things than that.
We should meet up in the real world.
That would be cool.
because I like having you as a friend.
Okay, we will.
I promise.
Well, ready to revive Pina? Yeah!
Pina, when you get back, I'll have
lots of stuff to tell you about.
About the amazing adventure I had.
And about this one day, when I got
to have my very own big brother.
I heard the sound of the
money that was a little late.
But once again, I'm strong.
And now, I'm so proud of the truth.
But the fact that the
fact that the reality is.
We can't wait to
see the future!
We can't wait to see the future!
We can't wait to see this.
Before we open the world?
Next time.
Murder in the safe zone.